

Filip Rastovic

PROFILE

Name	Filip Rastovic		
Year of Birth	1993		
Languages	English / Serbian		

CONTACT

Email	filiporastovic@gmail.com
Skype	filiporastovic

I grew up in Sremska Kamenica, suburban neighborhood of Novi Sad, where I also finished elementary school. As a kid I would spend my time reading comics, epic fantasy novels and playing video games. During high school I played guitar in the school orchestra and worked on technical support and special effects for the school theatre. During college I started developing small video games as a hobby and began my career as a freelancer utilizing everything I've learned through education and on my own. I'm passionate about technology and developing creative solutions to whichever problem I come across. I'm an avid reader and music lover.

Professional **Resume**

EXPERIENCE

2015 - present

Web Developer

HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript/PHP

Experience in converting Phothoshop designs into responsive web pages, designing and developing original websites, development of SAAS web applications and 2D video games. I put huge emphasis on aesthetic of every interaction user has with your software by making sure it all runs smoothly and beautifully.

2015 - 2016

Private Programming Lessons

OOP/Java

I lectured high school students teaching them basics of object oriented programming and Java.

EDUCATION

2012-2016

Faculty of Technical Sciences

Computing and Control Engineering

Department of applied computer science and informatics. I have understanding of data structures, computer architecture, object oriented programming, design patterns, software engineering methodologies and web development concepts. I'm also familiar with HCI concepts, machine learning and web security.

2008-2012

"Svetozar Marković" Gymnasium

Novi Sad

General course.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Responsive Web Design	Photoshop	JavaScript	HTML5
User Interface Design	Wordpress	jQuery	CSS3
User Experience Design	Zapier	php	Bootstrap4
	Mailchimp	git	SCSS/SASS

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS –



GAME DEVELOPMENT



CLASSIC LITERATURE



GUITAR



COMPUTERS



OUTDOORS



TRAVELS

Filip Rastovic filiporastovic@gmail.com